awakenthegreatnesswithin.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy | AwakenTheGreatnessWithin

This website is the property of Awaken The Greatness Within LTD. We take the privacy of all visitors to this Website very seriously and therefore set out in this privacy policy our position regarding certain privacy matters and the use of cookies on this Website.

This policy covers all data that is shared by a visitor with us whether directly via **www.** **awakenthegreatnesswithin.com**  or via email.

This policy provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you share with us, or that we collect from you either directly via this Website or via email.

##  **What Information Do We Collect**

In operating our Website we may collect and process the following data about you:

Details of your visits to our Website and the resources that you access including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblog statistics, and other communication data.

Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website, such as when you register to receive information such as a newsletter or contact us via the contact us page.

Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

##  **What Do We Use Your Information For**

The information we collect is primarily used to track the success of our Website. We endeavor to track which areas of the site are most popular and how we can serve our customer’s needs. The information is collected to keep track our of customer base and send weekly newsletters to those who opt-in (if you do not sign up to the newsletter, you will not be contacted weekly).

The information collected can be used to improve our Website so that you can get information that is better suited to you and your demographic and geographic location. The information collected helps us gauge what articles will be more appealing to our visitors.

The sole purpose of collecting information is to better serve our readers.

##  **How Do We Protect Your Information**

Security is of utmost importance to us and we make certain that we employ the most efficient and latest data protection software to keep our visitor’s data safe and secure.

##  **Use Of Cookies**

We may gather information about your general Internet use by using a cookie file that is downloaded to your computer. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically.  This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our Website and the service that we provide to you.

All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular areas of our Website.

Any advertising featured on this Website may also incorporate cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our Website.

We may contract with third-party service providers to aid us in analyzing our site visitors. The service providers have no ground to use the information we attain, but only to help improve our Website.

For more information on cookies you can read the guidance at [All About Cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

##  **Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?**

Any data we collect is not sold or traded. Information provided to us is kept secure, this does not include the third parties who aid us in keeping track and improving our Website, as long as they keep the data safe.

However, if there was a need to comply with law enforcement or implement our site policies, then data may be released to the appropriate parties where necessary.

##  **Third Party Links**

Any third-party links on our site that offer products or services have their own privacy policies, we bare no liability or responsibility from third-parties, as they have their own terms of use.

##  **California  Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance **

We are in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We will not distribute your information without your approval.

##  **Privacy Of Children**

We adhere to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not collect information from those who are under 13 years of age. our website is aimed at those who are 13 years old or older. If we do discover that we have collected information from someone who is under the age of 13, the information will be deleted from our database.

##  **Changes To The Privacy Policy**

If the policy is ever updated there will be an announcement on this page.

##  **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions in regards to the privacy policy you can get in touch with us via our email address.  
**Email:** success@awakenthegreatnesswithin.com
